万事俱备了哦
The car's full of gas.
你确定吗
You sure?
不确定又会怎样
And if I'm not?
你得把我买请柬上的钱还给我
You'll be paying me back for those damn invitations.
哦  那还是别麻烦了
Oh, well, then never mind.
泰德是个好人  爸爸
Ted is a wonderful man, dad.
是我遇到过第二好的人
He's the second greatest guy I ever met.
该轮到我们了
Guess that's us.
在这神圣的时刻  这两人即将
Into this holy estate, these two persons present
结为夫妻
Now come to be joined.
如有人知道任何
And so if any person may show just cause
他们不能结合的理由
Why they may not be joined together,
请现在提出来  否则请永远保持缄默
Let them speak now or forever hold their peace.
我就想听到这反应
That's what I like to hear.
你  西奥多·菲利普·泰勒
Do you, Theodore Philip Taylor,
是否愿意娶妮可·玛格丽特·马瑞为妻
Take Nicole Margaret Murray to be your wife
在上帝和在场见证人面前许下诺言
and promise before god and these witnesses
做她深爱的  忠诚的丈夫
To be her loving and faithful husband,
不论富有或是贫穷
In plenty and in want,
不论欢乐或是悲伤
In joy and in sorrow,
不论疾病还是健康
In sickness and in health,
直至生命终结
So long as you both shall live?
我
I--
泰德  别开玩笑
This isn't funny, Ted.
泰德
Uh... Ted.
你没事吧
Are you all right?
泰迪
Teddy.
Teddy!
泰德
Ted.
什么时候了
What time is it?
幸福时光
Happy time.
我还困着呢
I'm still asleep.
就当是在做梦吧
Just think of this as a dream.
那豪斯呢
What about House?
我是说做梦  不是指恶梦
I said a dream, not a nightmare.
他就在隔壁
He's in the next room.
睡得香着呢
Sound asleep.
埃斯特班
Esteban,
快起床
get up when you ready.
我刚遇见了邻居
I met the neighbors.
先生  请问您认识他吗
Sir, do you know this man?
我不要临时工  我要正式员工
I don't need a temporary. I need a permanent.
昨天
Yesterday.
请您务必
Please do.
-早上好  -一点都不好
- Good morning. - Hardly.
我的一个助理一小时前辞职了
One of my P.A.s quit an hour ago,
我得重新安排下个月的工作日程
And I have to reshuffle next month's schedule.
这不算什么
That's nothing.
我今早在陌生的床上醒过来
I woke up in the wrong bed this morning.
不管你睡的哪张床都是错的
Any bed you're in is the wrong one.
你妈妈可不是这么教你的
That's not what your mama said.
该死的
Oh! Snap.
我还是走了吧
I'll be going now.
去人事部
To human resources.
是他先开始的
He started it.
我睡在邻居家孩子的床上
It was the neighbor's kid's bed.
幸亏埃斯特班还喜欢跟妈妈睡
Luckily, Esteban still likes sleeping with mommy.
你到底喝了多少
How drunk were you?
烂醉
About yea drunk.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
你根本就不该喝酒  至少...
You shouldn't be drinking at all, much less--
你活像埃斯特班的妈妈
You sound just like Esteban's mom.
你今天出门诊吧
I need you in the clinic.
抱歉  我很忙
Sorry, I'm busy.
告诉我你有一个病例
Tell me you have a case.
就算你没有
You know, even if you don't.
我是有个病例
I have a case.
感觉挺有趣的  我接了
Sounds interesting. I'll take it.
我欠你一次
I owe you one.
现在告诉我  你没有病例
Now tell me you don't have a case.
我真有个病例
I really do have a case.
这下扯平了
We're even.
你们该去度蜜月呀
You guys know how to honeymoon.
这位是豪斯医生  失语症和昏厥
This is Dr. House. Aphasia and syncope.
他不能说话了
He can't speak.
"失语症"指的就是失声
"Aphasia" Is greek for loss of voice.
我们已经排除了感染  声带受伤或中风
We've ruled out infection, vocal cord damage, and stroke.
有很多家伙会在圣坛前昏倒
A lot of guys syncope at the altar.
这说的是"出现幻觉"
It's greek for "Having the vapors."
我们排除了所有常见的导致昏倒的原因
We ruled out all the common causes of fainting:
低血压  低血糖
Low blood pressure, hypoglycemia,
脱水
Dehydration.
别说"啊"
Don't say "Ah."
知道是什么病吗
Do you know what it is?
侧躺下  把衣服拉起来
Roll on your side and lift up your gown.
还有一项他们没检查
There's one thing they didn't test for.
检查什么
A test for what?
假装
Faking.
测试呈阳性
Test was positive.
我  我能说话了
I-I can--I can talk.
我没有在装
I-I wasn't faking.
现在我突然能说话了
My voice just came back right now.
你要说服的人可不是我
Hey, I'm not the one you have to convince.
我知道他没在装
I know he wasn't faking.
如果她相信  她可能就是个婚姻捍卫者
Well, if she's buying that, she might just be a keeper.
那昏厥又怎么解释呢
What about the syncope?
这...
Well, the--
她连这也相信了
Is she buying this too?
他为什么要装
Why would he fake anything?
发慌呗
Kryo podia.
这表示"犹豫不决"
It's greek for "Duh."
不过你还是会留着你们的婚戒
Still, you get to keep the engagement ring.
我觉得他不是装出来的
I don't think he was faking.
那是因为你比较容易上当
That's because you're more gullible than I am.
比如  我就不相信
For instance, I don't believe
是你取消了你们的开放式婚姻
That you called off your open marriage.
我敢肯定是你老婆叫停的
I believe your wife called it off,
而你没告诉她
And you called off telling her
你其实根本就不想取消
That you weren't calling it off.
男人决不会把婚姻的免死金牌当垃圾丢掉
A guy doesn't throw a golden ticket in the trash.
同理  那人也不该
The same way a guy doesn't give up
放弃收入颇丰的医疗事业来给你打工
A lucrative medical practice to come work for you?
这正是你出轨的原因
That's exactly why you dabble.
你这是在利用职场得意换取
You're compensating for your professional conquests
情场得意啊
With sexual ones.
我可没这么简单
I'm not that predictable.
比如说  你可能想不到
For example, you're probably not expecting me
今晚我想请你共进晚餐
To ask you out for dinner tonight.
不必了  谢谢
No, thanks.
你连考虑都不考虑吗
You won't even consider it?
我快速地考虑过了
I did, just very quickly.
事实是  自从我取消了开放式婚姻
The truth is, since I called this thing off,
我妻子一直心存感激
My wife has been very grateful
因此我可以迟点回家
And I could do with a down night.
如果我是和上司一起出去
If I go out with the boss,
没人会怪我
Nobody can blame me.
好吧  如果你带你老婆一起去
Okay. If you bring your wife.
不行  关键是
No. That's the point.
-我需要些...  -你撒谎
- I need a little-- - You're lying.
我没有
I'm not lying.
那我就不去了
Then I'm not going.
好吧  方缇尼餐厅  晚上8点半
Okay. Fontina at 8:30.
你相信我  对吧
You believe me, right?
我当然相信你
Of course I believe you.
那我们结婚吧
Then let's do it.
我们叫辆车  马上去礼堂
We'll tell a cab to take us to ac right now
把仪式举行完
And get it done.
你没开玩笑吧
You're serious?
你才刚从急诊室出来
You just walked out of the emergency room.
没错  我这不是出来了嘛
Exactly. I walked out.
感觉相当好
I feel great.
我们倒是有礼服可以穿
Well, we do have the clothes for it.
泰德  怎么了
Ted, what's wrong?
你...  怎么了
Are you--what's wrong?
我的天哪  谁来帮帮我们
Oh, my god. Can somebody help us?
拜托  拜托快点
Please! Please hurry.
呼气  我的老天
Just breathe. Oh, my god.
肯定还有更好的办法来取消婚礼吧
There's gotta be a better way to call off a wedding.
比如  写个微博
A tweet, for example.
胸腔积液
Pleural effusion.
你觉得他的肺也是假装的
You think his lung is faking it?
这积液起码有200毫升
There's at least 200 CCs of fluid in there.
好吧  那我们就当他所有的病症都是真的
Okay, let's say all his symptoms are real.
那解释下不用祷告  也没有圣母玛利亚
Explain how one of them suddenly went away
其中一个病症怎么就突然好了
Without using the words "Virgin" Or "Mary."
如果胸腔积液是系统紊乱引起的话
If the pleural effusion's caused by something systemic,
那这就能解释他另外两个症状
It could explain his other two symptoms.
不管你是否相信他
And so whether you believe him or not,
我们要做的就是搞清是什么引起胸腔积液
All we have to figure out is what caused the PE.
急诊室已经排除了感染
ER ruled out infection.
嗜酸细胞计数排除了寄生虫的可能性
Eosinophil count ruled out parasites.
他可没告诉我们  他在用什么药
A medication he's not telling us about.
你真的很不相信这个人  是吗
You really don't trust this guy, do you?
我连急诊的诊断都不信
I don't even trust the ER.
我们自己来排除感染的可能性
Let's rule out infections ourselves.
叩诊肺部  查出国史
Tap his lungs, send cultures,
查细胞是否癌变  测量血压
Run cytology for cancer, and check his blood pressure.
我们已经...
We already--
这次做的时候  讨论婚礼看看
This time, talk about nuptials while you do it.
去他家查查其它所有东西
Check his home for everything else.
他三个月前刚和未婚妻一起搬进去
He just moved in with his fiancee three months ago.
中毒反应显露迹象可能需要更长时间
Toxic exposure could take longer than that to manifest.
你去检查他的爱巢
You check his love nest.
你们两个去检查他时髦的单身公寓
You two check his swinging bachelor pad.
现在有别人在住是吗
That somebody else now lives in?
我估计是把
I assume so.
别打碎玻璃  别
Not the glass. No!
这地方看着很  60年代
The place looks like...1960s?
涂料里可能含铅
Could have lead paint.
你觉得一个27岁的家伙有异食癖吗
You think a 27-year-old has pica?
若这能让我们在屋主回来前离开这里的话
If it gets us out of here before the owner comes back,
没错
yes.
你会对那个可爱的理疗师说什么
What'd you tell that cute physio?
说我改主意了
That I changed my mind.
不  你没有
No, you didn't.
你比平时紧张
You're more nervous than usual.
因为这次破门而入的确"破"了
Because this b and e has actual b.
什么
Wha...
是个吊顶
That's a suspended ceiling.
你干什么呢
What are you doing?
我想看看上面是什么
I want to see what's above it.
更多的天花板
More ceiling.
由40年前的吸音板组成
Made of 40-year-old acoustic tile.
石棉肺  我喜欢
Asbestosis. I like it.
我到车里等你
I'll be in the car.
搞什么
What the hell?
没事
Uh, it's okay.
我们是医生
We're doctors.
没人在家  所以
Nobody was home, so--
我要打电话叫警察
Well, I'm calling the police.
你认识泰德·泰勒吗
Do you know Ted Taylor?
他过去住在这里
He used to live here.
是  他怎么了
Yeah. What about him?
他是我们的病人
He's our patient
在普林斯顿  普兰斯堡
at Princeton Plainsboro.
他没事吧
Is he okay?
我们觉得他可能有石棉肺
We think he may have asbestosis
因为你们的天花板材料
From your ceiling tiles.
他们不是石棉的  我搬来前检查过了
They're not asbestos. I had 'em checked when I moved in.
他病得多严重
How sick is he?
他是你的朋友吗
Is he a friend of yours?
曾经是
He was.
实际上  他曾做了我三年的男友
Actually, he was my boyfriend for three years.
-我不是同志  -真的吗
- I'm not gay. - Really?
因为这能解释你的临阵畏缩
'cause it would certainly explain the cold feet.
还有你的男友
Oh, and the boyfriend.
那么你是双性恋了
So you're bisexual?
不  我是直男
No, I'm straight.
寇特  你们遇见的那家伙  他是同志
Cotter, the guy you met, he's gay.
他看上我了  我就离开了
He had a crush on me. I left.
-三年后吗  -有可能
- After three years? - Well, it's possible.
和同志一起睡
It doesn't mean you're gay just '
不足以说明你是同志
cause the guy you're sleeping with is.
我们没有一起睡
We weren't sleeping together.
这有什么关系
What's this got to do with anything?
肺穿刺显示单核细胞增多症
Lung tap turned up mononucleosis.
急诊通常不查这个
ER doesn't routinely test for it.
这解释了胸腔积液
It explains the PE
还有  可能是没有临床症状的
And can be virtually asymptomatic.
我们好奇27岁的人怎么患上单细胞增多症的
So we got to wondering,  how does a 27-year-old get mono?
对于"接吻病"来说  你的年纪有点大
You're a little old for the kissing disease,
除非你的免疫系统有缺陷
Unless your immune system is compromised.
若有任何无保护性行为
If there's been any unprotected sex,
我们需要检测HIV
We'll need to test for HIV.
任何一种性行为都没有
There's been no sex of any kind.
好吧  我会找你未婚妻检测HIV
Okay. I'll go test your fiancee for HIV.
她是那种好奇心强的人吗
Is she the curious sort?
慢着
Wait.
可能有些接触
There may have been some contact,
不过  我不同志
But I'm not gay.
鸡奸  10大最常见家庭事故之一
Sodomy, one of the top ten most common household accidents.
我做过不少傻事
I did a lot of stupid things,
但我浪子回头了
But I turned my life around.
我和你们中的任何一个一样是直男
I'm as straight as any of you.
你没必要相信我
You don't have to believe me.
我就是说  你可以给我做检测
I'm just saying you can test me...
只要别告诉妮可
As long as you don't tell nicole.
管她什么事
What business is it of hers?
我不觉得他和异性恋女人结婚有什么不对
I don't see anything wrong with him marrying a straight woman.
这样说如何  他们两个都会不幸
How about, it'll make them both miserable?
和大多数异性恋婚姻一样
Just like most straight marriages.
他有权利生活  自由  还有不快乐
He's got the right to life, liberty, and unhappiness,
和我们一样
Like the rest of us.
别看我
Absolutely no reason to look at me.
我没说这是个好主意
I'm not saying it's a great choice.
-只是说这是他的选择  -还得是她的
- Just saying it's his choice. - It has to be hers as well,
不能只是因为她不知道他是同志
which it can't be as long as she doesn't know he's gay.
这现状得意保持的原因
Which is how it's gonna stay
因为我们没有权利去告诉她
Since we have no right to tell her.
就好象你从来没有违反过规章制度
Like you've never bent the rules.
你和男人约会  你和女人约会
You date guys. You date girls.
我推测到了一定时候  你得作出选择
I assume at some point, you're gonna make a choice.
关于我是什么样的人  我没有撒谎
I don't lie about who I am.
病人撒谎从来没有困扰过你吗
Patients lying never bothered you before.
此前  病人从没为了性取向撒谎
Patients weren't lying about their sexual orientation before.
那么只是问题针对个人时你才下判断
So you're only judgmental when it gets personal.
就因为他们太过脆弱无法面对现实
Does it bother me that people hurt others
我就该烦恼吗
Because they're too weak to face the truth?
是呀  对此很遗憾
Yeah. Sorry about that.
告诉我她不是在看我
Tell me she's not looking at me.
-他是阴性吗  -对
- He's negative? - Yep.
看来成为同志没有让他生病
Looks like being gay didn't make him sick.
那么或许是成为直男而导致的
So maybe being straight did.
检测是阴性  没有HIV
The test was negative. No HIV.
我告诉过你
I told you.
你没有告诉我们的是
What you didn't tell us
你是如何浪子回头的
Is how you turned your life around.
-会很困难  -没错
- It can be pretty hard. - It was.
完全靠自己是绝对不可能的
Downright impossible on your own.
我和一些人谈了
I talked to some people.
不仅仅是聊天  是吧
It was more than just talk, wasn't it?
我知道这是隐私
I know this is personal stuff.
我是来帮你的  不是揭发你的
I'm here to help you, not out you.
我接受了治疗
I had therapy.
转化治疗
Conversion therapy.
参加为期三周的强化康复露营
Went to a camp for three weeks of intensive rehabilitation.
看同志色情片的时候 给他注射催吐剂
They injected him with emetics while he watched gay porn.
阿扑吗啡吗
Apomorphine?
还是氯化锂  或着环磷酰胺
Or lithium chloride or cyclophosphamide.
他不知道
He doesn't know.
若那样还是没用
And when that didn't work,
他们给他注射雄性荷尔蒙
They shot him up with male hormones.
这样的化学伤害可以解释胸腔积液成因
A chemical assault like that could explain the pe.
电休克疗法可以解释其它的
And the ECT explains the rest.
他们给他用了电休克疗法为了把他扳直吗
They gave him electroconvulsive therapy to make him straight?
将他高尚的权利给电击出来
To zap the fabulous right out of him.
神经损伤导致失语症
Neural damage accounts for the aphasia.
电休克疗法不会造成神经损伤
ECT doesn't cause neural damage.
除非是在
Unless it was done
Liberace博士的猛男庸医营地
At Dr. Liberace's he-man quackery camp.
做个脑电图
Run an EEG.
看看他们是把他扳直了
See if they straightened him
还是把他脑子给搞乱了
or just scrambled him.
抱歉  我完全忘了
Sorry. I completely forgot.
我太太刚开始上陶艺课  每周二8点
My wife just started a ceramics class tuesdays at 8:00.
距离这里开车半小时
It's a half-hour drive from here.
10点半前她不会回来
She won't be back till 10:30.
她和她的朋友Marly一起参加的
She's taking it with her girlfriend Marly.
她希望能做个茶具
She hopes to make a tea service.
你想给她打电话吗
You want to call her?
不用  我已经短信她了
No need. I already texted her.
她来了
And here she is now.
我认为你还在和那个理疗师鬼混
I think you're still seeing the physio.
你车里有套备用西装
You've got a backup suit in your car.
不想把气味带回家
Don't want to be bringing home da stank.
好的  是  你是对的  所有事情
Okay, yes, you're right, about everything.
但求你  豪斯  别告诉她
But please, House. Don't tell her.
-你好 Rachel  -你好  豪斯医生
- Hi, Rachel. - Hi, Dr. House.
我不知道你会来
I didn't know you'd be here.
亲爱的  显然收到你的短信了
Hi, honey. Got your text, obviously.
我正要走
I'm just leaving.
我要去上陶艺课
I've got a ceramics class.
-真的吗  -我爱死了
- Really? - I love it.
还成功说服Chris报了一个
Even managed to talk Chris into signing up for one.
当然  他在初级班里
Of course, he's in the beginners' class.
你参加陶艺课了吗
You're in a ceramics class?
周五晚上  对吗
Friday nights, right?
周五晚上  听上去很有意思
Friday nights. Sounded like fun.
你该和Chris一起的
You should join Chris'.
对  我是该去的
You know, I should.
好了  该走了
Well, gotta go.
做茶具
Making a tea service.
我一定是在休息室睡着了
Hi, I must have fallen asleep in the lounge.
他们在干什么
What are they doing?
脑电图
An EEG.
为什么
What's it for?
我们在找神经损伤
We're looking for neurological damage
那可能导致他的症状
That could have caused his symptoms.
哪里来的损伤
Damage from what?
头部创伤
A head trauma.
他出意外了吗
He had an accident?
不是个意外
It wasn't an accident.
是在他遇见你之前
It was before he met you.
那么发生什么了  他当时住院了吗
Well, what happened? Was he hospitalized?
你该问问他的
You should ask him about it.
他们有结果了
They have the results.
似乎一切正常
Everything looks normal.
看这个
Look at this.
β波峰值形成
Beta waves are spiking.
这表示什么
What's that mean?
还不确定
I'm not sure.
他晕过去了  急救车
He's coding. Crash cart.
他怎么了
What's happening to him?
突发心脏停搏
He's having a heart attack.
充电  闪开
Charging. Clear.
心电图显示无异常
EKG showed no abnormalities.
那是什么引致他心脏骤停
So what caused the arrest?
有四种方法可以让心脏停跳
Four ways to stop a heart.
电生理的问题  供血不足的问题
Electrical problems, restricted blood flow,
以及血流到它不该去的地方
Blood where it shouldn't be,
休克  堵塞  出血
Shocks, blocks, or bleeds.
你这才三种办法
I think that's three things.
还有欺骗
And cheating.
噢  错了  不好意思
Oh, no. Sorry.
这是让人心碎的方法
That's how you break a heart.
我在特顿找到一个周五晚上的陶艺班
I found a ceramics class in Trenton on friday nights
人已经满了所以我妻子不能和我一起参加了
That was full so my wife couldn't join me.
诱发电位分析排除了休克
Ep study ruled out shocks.
现在你只要去找点陶博制造的陶器就行了
Now you just have to find some pottery by Taub.
越蹩脚的越好
The lamer it looks, the better.
那我们去做个血管造影
So we'll do an angio
看看是不是哪里堵塞或出血
to see if it's blocks or bleeds.
你应该当个医生
You should be a doctor.
我今晚会去个新开张的女同志酒吧看看
I'm gonna check out this new lesbian bar tonight.
你的生活真棒
Your life is awesome.
你要不要来
You want to come?
我正在告诉一个三十三岁的女人
I was telling a 33-year-old woman
她得了乳癌
that she has breast cancer.
-不  你没有  -你怎么知道
- No, you weren't. - How do you know?
因为如果是的话
Because if you were,
你需要看见她眼中的痛苦
you'd need to see the pain in her eyes
这样她才能看见你的眼里的关怀
so she could see the concern in yours.
你干吗安排我和我的那班子人约会
Why are you setting me up on dates with my team?
陶博约我是古怪
Taub asking me out was quirky,
但是十三约我像是小猫喵喵叫
But thirteen doing it is a barking cat.
我这样做是为你好
I'm doing it to help you.
给我安排个热辣美女  但又不能跟她睡
By setting me up with a hottie that I can't sleep with?
还偏偏是十三
And thirteen?
我和萨姆相处的时间越来越多了
I've been spending more time with Sam.
我知道你不好受
I know it's been hard on you.
我想如果有人和你作伴...
I figured if you had some company--
我不需要你的帮助
I don't need your help.
那就想成是在帮隔壁家那个四岁的娃
Then consider it helping our neighbor's four-year-old.
我给了他一块钱
I gave him a dollar.
你花了多少
How much did you have to pay?
没有
Nothing.
我就告诉他们你可能情绪低落
I just told them you might be feeling down
他们愿意陪你
and it was in their self-interest
是他们自己的想法
to keep you company.
一百块
100 bucks.
福曼跟我要两百
Foreman held out for 200.
豪斯  我很担心你
House, I'm worried about you.
你可能最终落得坐牢  甚至更糟
You could have ended up in jail or worse.
用罪恶感折磨你
Racking you with guilt.
所以是我干蠢事你给我奖赏
So I do something really stupid and you reward me.
读任何一本家长指南你都知道
Read any parenting manual.
这不是在帮我  这是帮你自己
That's not helping me. That's helping you.
好  我是为我自己  为了我爱情
Fine, I did it for me, for my relationship,
完全出于自私自利
out of pure self-interest.
好吧
Okay.
你愿意接受
You'll do it?
为了你
For you.
谢谢
Thank you.
不过这行不通的
It's not gonna work, though.
也许吧
Maybe.
不过在女同志酒吧呆一晚能有多糟
But how bad can a night out at a lesbian bar be?
嘿  感觉怎么样
Hey. How are you doing?
二十七岁就有心脏病
Heart attack at 27.
他们说你头部受过外伤
Um, they said you had a head trauma.
我从折叠梯上摔下来  撞了头
I fell off a stepladder and--and hit my head.
是个傻乎乎的意外
It was a stupid accident.
一次意外
An accident.
我们要为你的血管造影做准备了
We need to prep you for your angio.
安定会帮助你放松下来
Valium will help you relax.
我们要从你的股动脉穿入一根导线
We're gonna run a line through your femoral artery.
泰德  他心脏又停了吗
Ted? He's having another heart attack?
我想不是  他的心跳似乎很正常
I don't think so. His heart rate seems normal.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
你们不是在讨论结婚计划吧
You weren't discussing wedding plans, were you?
不是
No.
我想我只是...
I guess I just...
晕了
Fainted.
P.O.T.S.
体位性心动过速综合征
Postural orthostatic tachycardia syndrome.
他一竖起身子血压就急速下降
Bp plummets when he's upright,
一躺下就回复正常
Reverts to normal when he's lying down.
我们两次给他量血压  他都是躺着的
He was lying down both times we took his blood pressure.
持续低血压  可能诱发心脏骤停
Protracted hypotension could have induced his heart attack.
也能解释昏厥  以及他的失语症
Also explains the syncope. And his aphasia.
他原本直着身子  你让他躺下去
He was upright, then you laid him down on the bed
然后测了他的反应
to test him.
血压回复正常  他又可以发出声音了
Bp reverted to normal. Voice came back.
这和用针戳他毫不相干
Jabbing him with the needle had nothing to do with it.
产生P.O.T.S.的原因一般是
P.O.T.S. can be brought on
病毒或细菌感染  比如感染性单核血球病
by a viral or bacterial infection such as mono.
那就给他用足了氟氢可的松
So load him up with fludrocortisone.
你看没看你那陶艺班的课程描述
You didn't read your ceramics course description, did you?
看了  你也看了
Yeah. You did?
我保证你老婆看过
As I'm sure your wife did.
所以说我们都知道
So we all know
那个班现在在做七月四日[美国独立日]的主题
they're doing a fourth of July theme.
她会期待你的作品满是小星星
She'll be expecting something star-spangled.
妮可
Nicole?
是我
Yes?
寇特·马克林
Cotter Macklin.
我是泰德的一个老朋友
I'm an old friend of Ted's.
你好
Hi.
他怎么样了
How's he doing?
他的心脏出现了骤停
Um, he had a heart attack.
天哪
Oh, my god.
医生给他换了些新药
They have him on some new meds.
他现在睡得很深
Really knocked him out.
你呢  还坚持得住吗
Well, how are you holding up?
我没事  谢谢
I'm okay. Thanks.
我给他带了这个
Um, I brought this for him.
这是他全世界最最喜欢的东西了
That's his favorite thing in the whole world.
我知道
I know.
你没在婚礼上  对吗
You weren't at the wedding, were you?
是的  我没收到邀请
No, I-I wasn't invited.
泰德和我吵了一架
Ted and I had a-a falling out.
你们是怎么认识的
How did you know each other?
我们大四的时候认识的
Um, we met senior year of college.
我们一起合住了一段日子
Yeah, we--we shared a house for a while.
你们是室友
You were roommates?
有三年
For three years.
我很抱歉
I'm--I'm sorry.
我只是想念他了
I-I just miss him.
我想你应该离开
I think you should leave.
我不该那样
I shouldn't have done that.
现在
Now.
请你走吧
Please.
我希望他会好起来
I hope he gets better.
感觉如何
Hey, how are you feeling?
还不知道呢
Hmm. Don't know yet.
你各项指标情况良好
Your numbers look good.
我们会给你继续用这些药
We're gonna keep you on these meds.
你睡着的时候有人来看你了
You had a visitor while you were asleep.
是吗  谁
Oh, yeah? Who?
寇特  他是谁
Cotter. Who is he?
我毕业后和他合住一个房子
I shared a house with him after college.
我不知道他为什么会来
I don't know why he would show up.
-就这样吗  -是啊
- That's it? - Yeah.
为什么这么问  他说了什么
Why? What did he say?
我要你来告诉我  泰德
I need to hear it from you, Ted.
一天晚上  我喝得烂醉
One night, I got really drunk
然后我去床上睡觉
and I went to bed.
接着他来到我房间
And he came into my room.
就这样顺理成章地
One thing led to another.
这件事完全是个错误
The whole thing was a mistake.
你是说你和他发生了关系
Are you saying you had sex with him?
我当时醉得不省人事
I was drunk and confused.
你是同志吗
You're gay?
不是的
No.
我原以为我是
I thought I was.
我甚至下决心要告诉我的家人
I even made up my mind to tell my family.
我站在浴室的镜子前
I stood in front of the bathroom mirror,
想让自己兴奋起来
psyching myself up.
但我所感到的只有厌恶
All I could see was disgust.
也正是那个时候我明白了
And that's when I realized,
我厌恶的不是承认自己是同志
I didn't hate the thought of admitting I was gay
不是因为我感到羞愧
because I was ashamed.
我厌恶是因为我根本不是同志
I hated the thought because I wasn't gay.
就在那一天我寻求了帮助
And that was the day I went to get help.
这么说你并不是同志
So you're not gay?
他们治好了我  妮可
They cured me, Nicole.
头部受伤其实是说这件事
That's what all the head trauma is about.
我很抱歉我没有告诉你
I'm sorry I didn't tell you,
但这一切已经成为了过去
But it's--it's all in the past now.
不再重要了
It doesn't matter anymore.
怎么了
What is it?
我的头
Oh, my head!
他头疼得厉害
He's got severe headaches.
我也头疼
So do I.
是该叫牌还是加注看双料内听顺子呢
Should I call or raise with a double gutshot draw?
不对
No.
-有没可能是感染  -我们也这样想
- What about infection? - That's what we're thinking.
脑部感染可以解释头疼
Cerebral infection would explain the headaches,
可能引起直立性心动过速
could have caused P.O.T.S.
如果是真菌引起的  可能感染到心脏
If it's fungal, it could have spread to the heart.
我说的是你
I was talking about you.
我们的小陶绅士有没有风流快活过
Has the little gent been wearing a tent?
提醒我下  这跟你有什么关系
Remind me why that has anything to do with you.
生活分心工作也分心
A distracted person makes a distracted professional.
破坏我家庭就能让我专心咯
And destroying my marriage will help me focus.
很有可能
Probably.
做脊椎穿剌   化验脑脊液
Do a spinal tap. Run the CSF.
我说的还是你
Still talking about you.
不过如果你乐意  可以给病人也做
But you can do it on the patient, too, if you want.
她呢
What about her?
酒保
The bartender?
这里只有她不是来找乐子的
She's the only one who's not here for fun.
相信我  她不是异性恋
Trust me, she's not straight.
既然你同志雷达这么敏感
If your gaydar is so great,
怎么会看到病人男朋友才知道
how come you didn't know about the patient
他是同志的
till you met his boyfriend?
他是带着新娘来的
The guy walked in with his bride.
我一时没反应过来
It took me a while to rotate my dish.
他这么对她真是太过分了
It's unbelievable what he's doing to her.
你认为他不爱她
You don't think he loves her?
他或许是爱她的
He may love her,
可他有和其他男人上床的需求
but he needs to have sex with other men.
陶博是爱他妻子的
Taub loves his wife,
可他有和其他女人上床的需求
but he needs to have sex with other women.
是  陶博这么对他妻子也很过分
Yeah, it sucks what he's doing to her too,
可这不是一回事
But it's hardly the same.
我们的病人要对妻子忠诚
To be faithful to his wife,
就要否认自己的身份
our patient has to deny his identity.
陶博只需要
Taub just needs to...
克服生理需求
To resist a biological imperative?
面对甜点  直接拒绝要比
It is easier to say no to dessert
假装不爱吃甜点容易得多
than to pretend you don't eat.
从不节食之人如是说
Says someone who's obviously never been on a diet.
没错  我的生活如清风般自由
Oh, yeah. My life's a breeze.
你事业成功  人又聪敏
You're successful, smart,
有腿的东西都对你垂涎三尺
and you attract everything that moves.
你要总想着自己活不到50岁
If you want to focus on the fact that you're not gonna see 50,
谁也没办法
that's your choice.
知道吗  你说的对
You know what? I agree with you.
我顾影自怜是自找的  那你呢
My self-pity's optional. What about yours?
脑脊液感染化验阴性
CSF was negative for infection,
但他的头疼症状更重了
and his headaches are worse.
我们刚刚还谈论你呢
We were just talking about you.
拜托别了
Please don't.
不是直立性心动过速  又回到原点了
It's not P.O.T.S., so we're back to square one.
不完全是
Not quite.
做过脊椎穿剌之后头疼加剧
You did a spinal tap, but the headaches got worse.
吗啡用量已经快超标了
We're maxing him out on morphine.
他有漏液
He sprung a leak.
脑脊液正从穿刺处流失
He's losing CSF from the tap site.
是我们令头疼加剧的
We made his headaches worse?
事实上  只是你
Just you, actually.
仍然不能解释
That still wouldn't explain
他最初为什么头疼
why he got the headaches in the first place.
颅压过低是直立性心动过速的原因
The low pressure in his brain caused the P.O.T.S.,
不是后果
not the other way around.
把漏洞补好  给他输人造脑脊液
Patch the leak and top him up with artificial CSF.
好了  应该可以止住漏液
There. That should stop the leak.
疼痛应该很快就会减轻
You should be feeling some relief soon.
我跟我父母谈过了
I spoke to my parents.
他们怎么样
How are they doing?
他们仍然很担心
They're still worried.
告诉他们别担心
Well, tell them not to be.
一切都会好起来的
Everything's gonna be okay.
泰德
Ted?
怎么了
What's happening?
他中风了
He's stroking.
双眼瞳孔都有反射
Both eyes are responsive.
你的全名是什么
Tell me your full name.
西奥多·菲利普·泰勒
Theodore Philip Taylor.
-不是中风  -那是怎么回事
- This isn't a stroke. - Then what is it?
我这是怎么了
What's happening to me?
真的不是直立性心动过速
It's really not P.O.T.S.
我们真的回到原点了
We're really back to square one.
那么是谁假扮中风呢
So what's masquerading as a stroke?
顺便说一句  最差万圣节装束我投它
Voted the worst Halloween costume, by the way.
磁共振显示脑部供血正常
MRA showed no problems with blood flow to the brain.
排除了脑梗塞
rules out T.I.A.
结节病
Sarcoidosis?
胸透没有发现肺门肿块
Chest x-rays showed no hilar masses.
陶艺的事怎么样了
Any luck with the pottery?
不好弄
Wasn't easy.
网购了一套粗糙度合适的
Bought a suitably cruddy set
手工笛子和餐巾环
of fife and drum napkin rings online.
-硬皮病  -皮肤没问题
- Scleroderma? - Skin's fine.
抗核抗体阴性
A.N.A. was negative.
-买个东西有什么难的  -好多事
- So what did that set you back? - Too much.
有个疯子跟我抢着拍卖喊价
I got into a bidding war with some lunatic.
组织胞浆菌病
Histoplasmosis.
酶免疫测定阴性
EIA was clear.
215块可不算太高哦
Hey, could have gone a lot higher than $215.
你就是那个混蛋99号综合症吗
You're kissmyasthma99?
会不会是MELAS综合征
What about MELAS?
线粒体脑肌病
Mitochondrial encephalomyopathy,
表现为乳酸酸中毒和中风类似症候
Lactic acidosis, and stroke-like episodes.
NILLAS
Nillas.
不是  白痴  乳酸浓度稳定
No, idiot. Lactate levels are stable.
我们漏掉了什么
We're missing something.
该测的都测过了
We've run every test that makes sense,
能想到的都问过了
asked every question we can think of,
病史研究过十几遍
gone over his history a dozen times.
我们都知道他那病史有多少可信度
We know how much we can trust his history.
历史总是胜利者来书写
If history is written by the victor,
我们去哪里找真相呢
How do we find out what really happened?
找失败者谈谈  给他男朋友打电话
Talk to the loser. Call the boyfriend.
让他们在一个房间里
Let's get them all in the same room.
或者分开提问  别让他们难过
Or we could question them separately and not torture them.
或者让他们在一个房间里  得出真相
Or we could get them all in the same room and get the truth.
今晚的酒我和福曼请
Oh. Drinks are on me and Foreman tonight.
没空  要做子宫颈抹片检查
Can't. Pap Smear.
我们也不愿意
We don't want to do it either,
可威尔森付我们钱了
But Wilson already paid us.
肯定没好事
It's gonna suck.
我知道
I know.
几点在哪儿
Where and when?
有没有过突发性头晕
Any incidents of dizziness?
惊厥
Seizures?
昏厥
Blackouts?
除了婚礼上那次
Other than our wedding day.
如有的话我不早该告诉你们了
Don't you think I would have told you if there were?
我妹妹生日那次
My sister's birthday.
我喝多了
I was drunk.
你只喝了一杯马提尼酒
You had one Martini.
空腹喝的
On an empty stomach.
他当时坐在沙发上
Look, he was just sitting on the couch,
然后他  他就突然栽倒了
and then he...he... he fell over and that was it.
后来我睡了一觉就没事了
Well, once I slept it off, I was fine.
那天我一夜没睡
Well, I stayed up that night,
每15分钟就看他一次
checking on him every 15 minutes.
性生活呢
What about sex?
我跟我女朋友有性生活
Yes, I have sex with my girlfriend,
因为我不是同志
because I'm not gay.
-我们有性生活  -谢谢
- We have sex. - Thank you.
没出现过问题
No problems?
我们遇到过一些...
Um, well, there have been some...
-妮可  -问题
- Nic. - Issues.
勃起功能障碍
Erectile dysfunction?
这问题谁都遇到过
Every guy has it sometimes.
我们一起就没有过
We never had that problem.
那一定是因为泰德不喜欢女人
Gee, that must be because Ted doesn't like girls.
或者是血管疾病
Or because it's vascular.
我知道做过磁共振
I know we did an MRA,
但动脉疾病引起的局部供血不足
but arterial disease causing acute ischemia
可以解释心脏和神经系统的症状
could explain the heart, neuro symptoms,
甚至直立性心动过速
and maybe even P.O.T.S.
我可以提议做诊断测试吗
Might I suggest a diagnostic test?
阴茎体积描记仪测量
The penile plethysmograph measures
你阴茎内血流的变化
changes in blood flow in your penis.
可以显示血液循环异常
Tells us if there's a circulatory problem.
只要你在状态
You just need to be in the right...state.
中意哪一个
What's your pleasure?
我难受得要死
I feel terrible.
看什么也不会有用的
I-I don't think anything's gonna work.
那我们只好给你注射
Then we'll have to give you a shot.
注射位置可不太妙
Where you don't want to get one.
那就注射吧
Shot it is.
没人想跟着唱
Nobody wants to follow that.
夜色越来越迷人了
The night just keeps getting better.
敬威尔森
To wilson.
-威尔森  -威尔森
- Wilson. - Wilson.
看起来都没问题
Everything looks fine.
你确定吗
You sure?
从医学上讲  这是好事
Medically, that's good news.
你觉得热吗  你在出汗
Are you feeling feverish? You're sweating.
不  我感觉不爽  但不知道为什么出汗
No. I feel lousy, but I don't know why I'm sweating.
怎么了
What is it?
你不是在出汗
You're not sweating.
你是在分泌母乳
You're lactating.
不能告诉未婚妻他是基佬
Can't tell his fiancee he's gay,
但他怎么能告诉她他怀孕了呢
How is he gonna tell her he's pregnant?
他的理疗师给他用过激素
His therapists loaded him with hormones.
雄性激素不能下奶吧
Male hormones don't make you lactate.
除非它们破坏了你的甲状腺
Except they could screw up your thyroid.
用药是三个月前了
That was over three months ago.
而他昨晚才开始下奶
We just started milking him last night.
所以是其他东西破坏了甲状腺
So something else screwed up his thyroid.
甲亢  慢性甲状腺炎症
Graves, hashimoto's.
不是  他的促甲状腺激素水平很正常
Nope. Tsh was normal.
垂体瘤
Pituitary tumor.
也能解释
Could also explain
他的性问题
His libido
和心脏系统问题
And heart issues.
如果肿瘤足够大  他会头疼并昏厥
And if the tumor's big enough, his headaches and syncope.
除非我们  排除他是癌症的可能性
Except we-- we cleared him for cancer.
我没说"癌症"
Didn't say "Cancer."
泌乳素瘤可以是良性的
Prolactinomas can be benign.
检查他的泌乳素水平
Check his prolactin level,
然后给他做脑垂体核磁共振
then mri his pituitary.
听起来你们昨晚玩得不赖
Sounds like you had fun last night.
你相信奇斯吗
You believe chase?
我相信福曼
I believe foreman.
而且他们和你一起玩得很开心
And they had fun with you.
发生了什么
What happened?
我觉得他们可以成为我的朋友
I realized that they could be my friends.
你是认真的吗
You're serious.
然后我清醒过来
And then I sobered up.
你没有醉的太厉害
You weren't that drunk.
昨晚你成功找到了
You managed to find your way
回到自己小床上的路
Into your own little bed last night.
我觉得我在火箭飞船图案的床单上睡得更香
I think I sleep better in rocket ship sheets.
不  你想把这归罪于醉酒  这很容易
No, you want to blame this on the booze, but that's easy.
但改变却很难
Change is hard.
而智慧的意义就在于能分清
And wisdom is knowing the difference
你所能够改变的
Between what you can change...
和你与生俱来的区别
And what you were born with.
而怯懦就是把
And cowardice is labeling
不想改变说成是与生俱来
What you don't want to change as innate.
这场辩论我赢了
I was winning this argument.
脑垂体核磁共振成像...
Pituitary mri--
没有问题
Was normal.
头还疼吗
How are the headaches?
很疼
Terrible.
把你的头给我
Give me your head.
-你说什么  -我知道
- What the hell? - I know.
你是第一次听说
It's the first time you've heard that sentence
还能把头单独给人的
With a possessive pronoun.
这样  这样好多了
Oh, wow, that-- that's better.
好了  够了
Okay, enough.
很酷吧
How cool is that?
你有小脑延髓下疝畸形
You have a chiari malformation,
你的颅骨基部有一处狭窄
A narrowing in the base of your skull
阻断了脑脊液的流动
That can cut off csf flow.
但不会有问题
But it wasn't a problem
除非核武器训练营给你用电休克疗法
Until the ect at breeder boot camp
来导致你大脑膨胀  造成狭部堵塞
Caused your brain to swell just enough to plug the opening.
当你的大脑压迫垂体时
And when your brain pressed up against your pituitary,
就会让你开始泌乳
It signed you up for la leche league.
你还是不能为你的女人而勃起
You still won't be pitching a tent for your lady,
只是因为  你知道的  她是个女人
But that's just because, you know, she's a lady.
直立效应是模仿体位性心动过速综合症
Its orthostatic effect was mimicking p.O.T.S.
又是个神秘的克里斯托弗·沃肯
It also does an uncanny christopher walken.
不幸的是  如果按POTS治疗
Unfortunately, if you treat it like P.O.T.S.,
病情会更恶化
It gets worse.
如果那样的话  哎呀
So as far as that goes, oops.
最好的治疗方式是手术  马上为你安排
Proper treatment is surgery. We'll get you in right away.
我怎么会得这病的呢
So how did I get this thing?
蛮横的母亲
Overbearing mother.
开玩笑  小脑延髓下疝畸形是天生的
Kidding. Cm's congenital.
像很多其他事情一样  你是与生俱来的
Like so many other things, you were born that way.
我想你可能快吃完了  所以...
I thought you might be running low, so...
谢谢
Thanks.
我不会再回来了
I'm not coming back.
泰德  这是个错误
Ted, this is a mistake.
我知道你受伤了  我很抱歉
I know you're hurting, and I'm sorry.
我不是说伤害她
I'm talking about hurting her.
我爱她
I love her.
泰德
Ted.
谢谢你的支持
Thank you for your support.
我们俩都很感激你
We both really appreciate it.
祝你好运
Good luck.
你知道我刚才在想什么吗
You know what I've been thinking?
三周后就是你的生日了
It's your birthday in three weeks.
你觉得我们再预定教堂一次
What do you say we rebook the church
来个双喜临门怎么样
And make it a doubleheader?
我不知道  泰德
I don't know, ted.
不到一周前  我们站在圣坛前
Less than a week ago we were standing at the altar,
欢喜至极
Perfectly happy.
什么都没改变
Nothing's changed.
真的吗
Really?
我仍爱你
I still love you.
你还爱我吗
Do you still love me?
是的
Yes.
但是...
But--
这就行了啊
Then that's all that matters.
但我想你还是爱他的
But I think that you still love him.
我不是同志  妮可
I'm not gay, nicole.
我向你发誓
I promise you.
你怎么向我发誓
How can you promise me that?
因为我相信我们必须
Because I believe that we get
选择我们得生活方式
To choose how we live our lives,
而且我做出了我的决定
And I've made my choice.
所以现在我必须做出我的决定
So now I have to make mine.
妮可
Nic.
对不起
I'm sorry.
妮可
Nic.
不  不
No. No.
我不是在说再见
I'm not saying good-bye.
是的
Yeah.
我想娶你
I want to marry you.
我得娶你
I have to marry you.
妮可
Nic!
星期五晚上了
It's friday night.
我取消了
I called it off.
这次是真的
For real this time.
下次放你假
Frees you up for the next one.
一天一次
One day at a time.
餐巾环
Napkin rings.
我用它来表示感谢
My way of saying thanks.
为了破坏你家庭而道谢吗
For trying to wreck your marriage?
为了拯救它
For trying to save it.
就给我个餐巾环吗
And I get napkin rings?
很贵呢
Expensive ones.
我雇了个人
I hired a replacement.
做我的私人助理
For my p.A.
她看起来不错
She seems great.
-干得不错  -你也是
- Good work. - You too.
你的病人明天回家
Your patient's going home tomorrow.
他没有家
He doesn't have a home.
你想吃点什么吗
You want to grab a bite to eat?
是威尔森让你来的吗
So wilson got to you too?
不  是我自己
No. This is just me.
-卢卡斯呢  -他加班
- Lucas? - Working late.
我请客
I'm buying.
我不太饿
I'm not that hungry.
好吧
Okay.
我只希望我们还是朋友
I just want us to be friends.
有意思
Funny.
那是我最不想要的结果
That's the last thing I want us to be.